

CONTACTS

Plot 35, Farm 428, Harkerville, Plettenburg Bay address

ilexssa @gmail.com Email

079 411 4494 / 044 532 7530 Cell / Tel/Fax

PERSONAL PROFILE

Holly Susan Stella Austen Full names

> 6011170168083 I.D. Number

17 November 1960 - 53yrs Date of Birth / Age

Licence: Code 08
Drivers Licence

Married – 21 February 1994

Marriage Status

A daughter who is studying in UCT – 18 yrs old Dependents

> Guy Hamilton Austen Spouse Full Names

21 February 1967 – 47 yrs Birth Date/Age

My husband is a diabetic and was diagnosed in 2012 with advanced Primary Progressive Multiple Sclerosis. He is no longer able to work.

EDUCATION

Senior Certificate - 1977 Pretoria High School for Girls

Typing and Bookkeeping Liefs Commercial College - 1978

CNA Pretoria Provincial Office in-house Courses C.N.A. Ltd 1989 - 1990

Paralegal Practioner - 2014 University of Cape Town Certified Short Course

EXPERIENCE

Woolfsons Pharmacy & Berrys Phy – 1977 - 1979 Foschini Stores – 1979 - 1980 The Pretoria News – 1980 - 1981 Home Executive – 1981 - 1985 C.N.A. Ltd Pretoria Provincial Office – 1985 - 1993

*Team Tech Services – 1993 - 2001 *TTS WebDesign – 2001 - 2003 *FlowerShop.co.za – 2003 - 2014

I have been self-employed since 1993. My husband & I have been sole proprietors of the above three business'. Flowershop was programmed by him & I did sales and administration.

We at the same time homeschooled our daughter from Grade 1 through to Grade 12, with her finishing on Cambridge AS levels.

I do not smoke (I gave up smoking in 1998 after 20 years), and I enjoy driving and cycling. I love the scenic routes.

I am adaptable and determined to make a success of all that is put in my path.